

PROFILE

Web Developer with 9 years of experience for multiple domains including business, healthcare, e-commerce, etc.

Blockchain developer with 4 years of experience for Dapps, NFT, Web3 projects etc.

Skilled in ether.js and web3.js with hardhat and truffle

LINK

<u>website</u>

CONTACT

Address: 500 Rexdale Blvd, Toronto, Ontario(ON) Canada

PHONE: (805) 214-8119

EMAIL:

jasonli890218@gmail.com

LANGUGAE

English Chinese

HOBBIES

Football Piano

JASON LI

Blockchain Developer

EDUCATION

Western University

August 2008 – May 2013

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science

WORK EXPERIENCE

Modea (Junior Web Developer)

May 2013 - March 2017

Developed web application frontends related with healthcare using React.js and Vue.js.

John Abbott College (Full Stack Developer)

March 2017 - June 2018

Built frontends for several projects using React.js and Vue.js and backends using node.js

Scorpbit Inc - An SCT Group Company (Blockchain Developer)

June 2018 - May 2020

Developed smart contracts with Solidity using Remix and Hardhat to deploy on several blockchain networks Created and deployed ERC20, ERC721 tokens to blockchain networks

Pharos Production (Blockchain Developer)

May 2020 - May 2022

Built Dapps, NFT and Web3 projects based on ethereum network using Web3.js and Ether.js according to requirements and development guidelines

SKILLS

